{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "In which year Middleware was founded?",
      "options": ["2023", "2022", "2021", "2024"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How many products does Middleware have?",
      "options": ["8", "12", "17", "13"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Middleware used for?",
      "options": [
        "For tracking users",
        "For monitoring",
        "Spying on users",
        "Observability Platform"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How many followers are on LinkedIN page of middleware?",
      "options": ["7.5K", "8K+", "7K", "God knows"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the recent hire in Middleware.io?",
      "options": ["Rajuji", "Mohit", "Malay", "Sagar"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What happens if you don’t instrument your app with Middleware?",
      "options": [
        "Your app cries silently",
        "Latency grows legs and runs away",
        "You get haunted by unmonitored microservices",
        "You don’t see anything — and that’s the scariest part"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What technology is used in Browser Test?",
      "options": [
        "AWS Fargate",
        "Azure Container Instances",
        "GCP Worker",
        "Cron Jobs"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who has most commits in bifrost?",
      "options": ["Rajuji", "Milan", "Kaushal", "Keval"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which product is used for improving MTTR?",
      "options": [
        "Log Monitoring",
        "Real User Monitoring",
        "APM Monitoring",
        "Synthetic Monitoring"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these is not Middleware.io product?",
      "options": [
        "LLM Observability",
        "Synthetic Monitoring",
        "Cloudwatch Monitoring",
        "Database Monitoring"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which programming language is heavily used in Middleware?",
      "options": ["Typescript", "Go", "Javascript", "Python"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which database is used for logs?",
      "options": ["Clickhouse", "MongoDB", "Quickwit", "Cassandra"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which cloud product is used in Middleware.io for synthetic agent?",
      "options": ["Azure Container", "AWS EC2", "Azure AKS", "Digital Ocean"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the top visited page in Middleware website as of now?",
      "options": ["Ops AI", "Real User Monitoring", "APM ", "Log Monitoring"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How many integrations Middleware supports?",
      "options": ["57", "128", "111", "145"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    }
  ]
}
